

Software Engineer seeking roles in Software Development, Application Programming, Application Maintenance, Project Management, Requirement Analysis, Object Oriented Programming, C++, Shell Scripting, AWS, Oracle PL/SQL, GIT, Linux, Jenkins, PRO*C, Kenan FX



Current Designation: Software Engineer -Software Total Experience: 3 Year(s) 3 Month(s)

Development Highest Degree: B.Sc [information technology]

Current Company: Amdocs
Current Location: Pune

Pref. Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore, Gurgaon, Pune Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Single/unmarried

Key Skills: Software Engineer, Software Developer, Software Development, Application Programming, Application Maintenance, Project Management, Requirement Analysis, Object Oriented Programming, C++, Shell Scripting, AWS, Oracle

PL/SQL,GIT,Linux,Jenkins,PRO*C,Kenan FX

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 19-Jan-21 Last Modified: 19-Jan-21

Summary

Developer with over 3 years of experience in C++ template metaprogramming, Oracle, shell scripting and RPA tool. Recognized consistently for performance excellence and contributions to success in telecom industry. Strengths in Kenan FX billing , payment system and backed by DevOps technologies.

Work Experience

Amdocs as Software Engineer -Software Development Aug 2017 to Till Date

Experienced developer in telecom domain for distributed, client-server and service oriented environment.

Collaborated on all stages of software development lifecycle i.e from analysis, implementation to

production releases. Strong experience in Object Oriented Programming

technologies

Flow designing using RPA tool

Automation of production processes to save

manpower and revenue

Strong experience in telecom billing, payment

system

Experience with DevOps concepts

Project Details Feb 2020- Present Sky Italia | Developer

As part of scrum team, I'm sole responsible for all type of developments of entire payment modules in

Sky consisting of 48 custom modules written in C++ and Pro*C

Aug 2017- Jan 2020

Bharti Airtel | Developer

Worked for enhancements/fix of multiple Kenan modules written in Pro*C for postpaid mobility and telemedia.

Responsible for enhancements in multiple rating, dunning/collection modules due to migration from

Kenan FX 1.2 to Kenan FX 3.0

Multiple rewards from client for more than 300 automations of production processes which helped in saving revenue in millions, reduced manpower and less dependency on human interaction.

Education

UG: B.Sc (information technology) from Veer Surendra Sai University Of Technology - Burla in 2017

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version Last Used Experience
C++	
Shell Scripting	
AWS	
Oracle PL/SQL	
GIT	
KENAN FX	
Linux	
Jenkins	

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English				
Hindi				
Odia				

Affirmative Action

Work Authorization

Physically Challenged: No

Job Type: Permanent

Employment Status: Full time